

LARION PETRU EUSEBIU

Freelance Frontend Developer - UpWork

Age 38 from lasi, married

Contact details

Email: sebilarion@gmail.com Tel: +40770032715

Address: lasi

About me

I studied programming in high school and during university, but I have worked in another field so far.

Last year, I wanted to see if I could learn on my own and return to this industry. I started with frontend technologies and I liked the experience. I gained knowledge of HTML, CSS and Javascript.

I managed to create a small Angular-based application from scratch and received positive feedback.

At the same time, I worked remotely on the frontend of a startup project for QSite Solutions in Bucharest. In these small projects, I learned to work with Visual Studio Code, BitBucket, Trello, Git.

This year, I also worked remotely on a project for Next View Digital Marketing Agency LTD in Leicester, UK. In this project I learned TailwindCss and Vue js.

I think my past education will also help me do well in the IT industry, as I have already worked with databases and studied programming languages in the past.

I learn fast, I work hard and I am determined to do a good job.

I hope I can stand a chance to prove it.

Professional experience

Experience by

Sales: 11 months

departments

Administrative / Logistics: 12 years and 9 months Telecommunications : 14 years and 3 months

IT Software: 1 year and 10 months

Service / Maintenance: 12 years and 1 month

Sep 2020 - present

Freelance Frontend Developer - UpWork

4 months

Remote (from home) | IT Software | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities

Based on provided designs I developed web pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Angular

Material.

Some examples can be seen on www.eusebiularion.tech

Acquired skills and knowledge:

 $HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, GitHub, trello, ReactJS, Angular \, Material, \, Visual \, studio \, code, \, vue.js, \, and \, code, \, vue.js, \, descript \, code, \, descript \,$

Freelance Frontend Developer - Project Based-Next View Digital Marketing Agency LTD,

vuejs, Tailwind, JavaScript(Angular 2), Git(BitBucket)

Aug 2020 - present

Leicester, UK

5 months

Remote (from home) | IT Software | IT / Telecom

www.ejobs.ro contact@ejobs.ro I recreated the Delete Agency blog, using Tailwind CSS and VueJS. This project is made in HTML5, Tailwind CSS, VueJs. It fully preserves the functionality of the original site, having all the active links (it is a complete blog model, with social media links, etc.).

Is a fully responsive, mobile-first website. Subsequently, it was integrated in a CMS (Wordpress) and customized according to the client's wishes.

Acquired skills and knowledge:

JavaScript, GitHub, HTML5/CSS3, vuejs, Tailwind

Feb 2019 - present

Freelance Frontend Developer - Project Based-Qsite Solutions, Bucuresti

1 year and 11 months

Remote (from home) | IT Software | IT / Telecom

I worked in 2 projects with them.

On the first project I implemented an application in Angular 7, that was at a later point integrated into a CRM project. This application had 3 modules: one for products, another one for categories and one for invoices. Every section was a fully functional CRUD. The storing of data was flexible: both JSON files and db were supported. For styling I used Bootstrap on this project.

The second project was a platform dedicated to farmers for business management and selling products on the market. I worked on 2 modules of this project.

The project was made in Angular 7, and for the styling we used Angular Material.

Acquired skills and knowledge:

JavaScript, bitbucket, typescript, trello, HTML5/CSS3, material design, Angular Material, Angular 7

Nov 2008 - present

DTH Regional Coordinator, North East Area - SC RCS RDS SA

12 years and 2 months

Iasi | Telecommunications | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities:

- o Coordination of the personal activity of the DigiTV Service and Sales in the allocated area;
- o Elaboration / revision of the working procedures from the services of the department and Sales DigiTV
- o Verifying the activity of DigiTv partner installers in the allocated area;
- o Verification of local stocks of equipment and materials and reports based on periodic or demand superiors;
- o Evaluation of subordinated employees;
- o Making the established targets;

Acquired skills and knowledge:

Leadership, Project management, Training skills, Team leadership, Team Management, Sales, kpi, coaching and training

Nov 2008 - present

Fixed Point Service and Repairs Regional Coordinator, North East Area - SC RCS RDS SA

12 years and 2 months

lasi | Service / Maintenance | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities:

- o Coordinating the activity of the equipment repair personnel in the assigned area;
- o Elaboration / revision of the working procedures within the equipment repair department
- o Verifying the activity of the technicians in the allocated area.
- o Checking local stocks of equipment and materials and reporting the situation to superiors periodically or on demand:
- o Preparation of the necessary monthly parts and materials needed for repairs and their transmission to superiors hierarchically whenever necessary.
- o Maintaining the relationship with the suppliers of parts and materials needed for repairs.
- o Evaluation of subordinated employees;
- o Making the established targets;

Acquired skills and knowledge:

Leadership, Team Management, electronics repair

Mar 2008 - present

Courier Logistics department coordinator, lasi Branch - SC RCS RDS SA

12 years and 10 months

Iasi | Administrative / Logistics | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities:

- o Receipt of invoices and advertising and marketing materials related to the lasi branch.
- o Establish distribution areas for subordinated couriers and hand over invoices, advertising and marketing materials for distribution.
- o Checking the daily activity of the couriers so that they comply with their maximum distribution times.
- o Verifying the correctness of the daily delivery of the correspondence made by the couriers.

o Verification of complaints received from customers and setting penalties for couriers who did not distribute correspondence according to the procedures.

o Evaluation of subordinate employees

Acquired skills and knowledge:

Team Management, team coordination, logistics management

Apr 2008 - Jul 2011

Operator Validation and Data Entry - Responsible for Digi Corrections - SC RCS RDS SA

3 years and 4 months

lasi | Telecommunications | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities:

- o Registration of documents in internal applications;
- o Verifying the correctness of the recordings made in the internal applications;
- o Correction of errors arising from the introduction of documents in internal applications;

Acquired skills and knowledge:

Team work, ambitious and eager to learn new things, attention to detalis, Microsoft Word and Excel

Apr 2008 - Mar 2011

Responsible for supplying points of presence, lasi branch - SC RCS RDS SA

3 years

Iasi | Administrative / Logistics | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities:

- o Checking the equipment stocks and reporting the situation to the superiors periodically or on demand;
- o Preparation of equipment requirements and supply of points of presence

Acquired skills and knowledge:

stock control, Microsoft Excel, logistics and inventory management

Mar 2007 - Aug 2008

DTH Local Coordinator - SC RCS RDS SA

1 year and 6 months

Iasi | Telecommunications | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities:

- o Verifying the activity of DigiTv partner installers in the allocated area;
- o Checking local stocks of equipment and materials and reporting the situation to superiors periodically or on demand:
- o Making the established targets;
- o Promote the company's image through a positive, proactive and customer-oriented attitude.

Sep 2006 - Mar 2007

DTH Sales Representative - SC RCS RDS SA

7 months

lasi | Telecommunications | IT / Telecom

Responsibilities:

- o Ensuring the relationship with the clients of the company, through activities of sale of DTH services
- o Developing the client portfolio and maintaining a high level of satisfaction with them

Acquired skills and knowledge:

Sales skills, good comunication skills, direct sales

Nov 2005 - Sep 2006

Comercial agent - SC MIKE DISTRIBUTION SRL

11 months

Iasi | Sales | Commerce / Retail

Newly established company, franchise of SC Mike International SRL one of the most important cosmetic importers in Romania

Responsibilities, Achievements

- o Establishing and developing the direct relationship with clients
- o Take orders and coordinate the delivery
- o Ensuring the merchandising of brands
- o Receiving invoices and maintaining the minimum level of credits in the market

Acquired skills and knowledge:

Sales, good comunication skills, selling products and services

Education

2009 - 2013 Bachelor's degree - Alexandru Ioan Cuza University

Management and business administration | lasi

2001 - 2005 Undergraduate - Gheorghe Asachi Technical University

Automation and computers | lasi

1997 - 2001 High School / Vocational school - Anghel Rugina Economic College

Mathematical Informatics | Vaslui

Skills

General skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript(Angular)

Skills from work experience

Team work, ambitious and eager to learn new things, attention to detalis, Microsoft Word and Excel, Leadership, Team Management, electronics repair, team coordination, logistics management, Project management, Training skills, Team leadership, Sales, kpi, coaching and training, stock control, Microsoft Excel, logistics and inventory management, Sales skills, good comunication skills, direct sales, selling products and services, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, GitHub, trello, ReactJS, Angular Material, Visual studio code, vue.js, vuejs, Tailwind, JavaScript(Angular 2), Git(BitBucket), bitbucket, typescript, HTML5/CSS3, material design, Angular 7

Foreign languages

English - Medium

Other info

Trainings

JavaScript: The Advanced Concepts

period Jun 2020 - Dec 2020

Learn modern, advanced JavaScript practices and be in the top 10% of JavaScript developers.

The Complete Web Developer in 2021: Zero to Mastery

period Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Learn to code and become a Web Developer in 2021 learning HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node.js, Machine Learning & more!

Angular (Full App) with Angular Material, Angularfire(+ Firebase and Firestore) & NgRx

period Dec 2019 - Feb 2020

Angular 2- The Complete Guide

period Sep 2018 - Mar 2019

The Complete Web Developer Course

period Mar 2018 - Jul 2018